Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
H.E. Butti Bin Bishr Collection
Circa 1960 - 1975
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
Butti Bin Bishr ((Humaid)), 1941-2011
AD.MC.093
723 Photographic Prints 470 loose photographic prints, 1 negative and 7 albums containing 252 photographic prints. Mainly colour photographs with some black and white. Some with significant curling or warping, but none that prohibit digitization.
36 Leaves 36 letters, memos, certificates and ID documents
E-records AD_MC_093
Content Description
A (digital surrogate) collection of 723 photographs and 36 related documents from the collection of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, created and collected during his time working in the court of H.H. Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan in the 1960s and early 1970s.
Biographical / Historical
HE Butti Bin Bishr, who was born on Muharram 21, 1360 AH (May 18, 1941 AD), passed away on Rabi al Awwal 1432 (February 22, 2011). After working as the director of the Oman Bank in Al Ain, HE Butti Bin Bishr occupied a number of different administrative positions at the court of the late HH Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, before becoming private secretary and then the director of his Office.
Conditions Governing Access
Digital surrogates only are held by the repository. Please contact Akkasah Photography Archive, akkasah@nyu.edu +971 2628 5531
Photographic Prints; Political Life; United Arab Emirates; United Arab Emirates -- History -- 20th century; Political Leadership
- Diplomatic and Political Engagements of the UAE 1972
  - The front cover of "Diplomatic and Political Engagements of the UAE 1972.", Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; United Arab Emirates; Pakistan; Unknown Locations; Syria
  - The inside front cover of "Diplomatic and Political Engagements of the UAE 1972.", Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Pakistan; United Arab Emirates; Syria; Unknown Locations
  - An advertisement page in an Apples Self-Adhesive Album., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Pakistan; Tokyo, Japan; Advertisements; Printed Materials; United Arab Emirates; Syria; Unknown Locations
  - The blank index of "Diplomatic and Political Engagements of the UAE 1972.", Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Pakistan; Printed Materials; United Arab Emirates; Syria; Unknown Locations
  - Top: From the left around the table: H.E. Khalaf Bin Ahmed Al Otaiba, H.E. Sheikh Ahmad Al Hamed, H.E. Ahmed Bin Haisa Al Saeedi, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh Ahmed Bin Ali Al Thani, Emir Sheikh Issa Bin Salman Al Khalifa of Bahrain at a conference concerning the unification of the United Arab Emirates. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) with Sheikh Ahmad Bin Ali Al Thani of Qatar (right) at a conference concerning the unification of the United Arab Emirates., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref4_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Officials; Government; Men; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gatherings; Royalty; Politics; Head Covers/Veils; Cigarettes; Presidents; Flags; Tea/Coffee; Political Leadership; Sheikh, Ahmad bin Ali bin Abdullah bin Jassim bin Mohammed Al Thani, 1922-1977; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Top: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with Sheikh Ahmed Bin Ali Al Thani of Qatar (right) at a conference concerning the unification of the United Arab Emirates. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) with Emir Issa Bin Salman Al Khalifa of Bahrain at a gathering., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Officials; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Group Portraits; Royalty; Government; Gatherings; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Jewelry; Politics; Arabic Writing; Flags; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Presidents; Group Portraits; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the left: H.E. Maolum Al Otaiba, an official in the Abu Dhabi government, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan shaking hands with Jafaar Nimeiri, and an unidentified man at the reception of the Sudanese delegation in the UAE., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Royalty; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Presidents; Officials; Gatherings; Clocks/Watches; Furnishings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Jafaar Nimeiri and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr greeting one another in a crowd during the arrival of the Sudanese delegation in the UAE., Circa 1970-1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Men; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Presidents; Officials; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Group Portraits; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Hats; Gatherings; Crowds; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009
  - A group portrait including H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr on a personal trip in Murree, Pakistan., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref4_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Men; Presidents; Murree, Pakistan; Group Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Buildings; Forest/Woodlands; Head Covers/Veils; Color Photography; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top left clockwise: a crowd of men gathered for the arrival of the Sudanese delegation to the UAE; From the right: a group portrait of H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.E. Sheikh Ahmad Al Hamed, and an unidentified man; and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) greeting Jafaar Nimeiri (left)., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Officials; Presidents; Group Portraits; Men; Crowds; Gatherings; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Tea/Coffee; Furnishings; Electricity; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009
  - Top: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with Emir Issa Bin Salman Al Khalifa of Bahrain, with coffee and beverages on the table. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan walking with Jafaar Nimeiri next the Abu Dhabi police., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Facial Hair; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Presidents; Royalty; Tea/Coffee; Furnishings; Flags; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Airports; Guns; Weapons; Officials; Gatherings; Telephones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - Top: From the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) and two other men performing at an Al Ayala dance. Bottom: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan waving to a crowd of people during the arrival of Jafaar Nimeiri., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Gatherings; Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Presidents; Guns; Weapons; Dancing; Royalty; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Political Leadership; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top left clockwise: two views of performances to celebrate the arrival of the Emirati Delegation to a country overseas, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) talking with a man., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Performing Arts; Dancing; Costumes; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Hats; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Gatherings
  - From the top left clockwise: a group of school girls dancing with the UAE and Kuwait flags to celebrate the opening of a new school; a woman and man performing in costumes at the reception of the Emirati Delegation overseas; H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Bin Hamed Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Tahnoun Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and an unidentified man performing at an Al Ayala dance., May to June 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Unknown Locations; United Arab Emirates; Dancing; Flags; Performing Arts; Children; Costumes; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Singing/Singers; Gatherings; Balloons; Facial Hair; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Arabic Writing; Banners; Royalty
  - From the top down: a gate with a welcoming message for Sheikh Zayed, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr flipping through a book in his office in Al Ain, From the left: H.E. Ahmed Al Nasroud, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr greeting Emir Issa Bin Salman Al Khalifa of Bahrain, and H.E. Sheikh Ahmad Al Hamed (middle) at the Abu Dhabi Airport., March to May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Individual Portraits; Offices; Officials; Workers; Signs/Signposts; Arabic Writing; United Arab Emirates; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Telephones; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Flags; Men; Group Portraits; Royalty; Airplanes; Airports; Transportation; Facial Hair; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Gatherings; Books; Parks; Presidents; Royalty; Political Leadership; Royalty
  - From the top left clockwise: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan receiving a bouquet during the UAE delegation's visit to Syria, with H.E. Sheikh Ahmad Al Hamed, H.H. Sheikh Mubarak Al Nahyan, and Hafez Al-Assad behind Sheikh Zayed; members of the Syrian military receiving H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan; and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with Hafez Al-Assad., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Airports; Syria; Men; Group Portraits; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Furnishings; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Crowds; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Color Photography; Flags; Cigarettes; Smoking; Royalty; Ceremonies; Political Leadership; al-Assad, Hafez, 1930-2000; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top down: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with an official during the UAE visit to Syria; H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan being received by Hafez Al-Assad in a crowd (middle), including H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi (behind Assad), H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (left of Romaithi, wearing a suit), H.E. Sheikh Ahmad Al Hamed (left of Sheikh Zayed, wearing sunglasses), H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front, next to bouquet); and the Sudanese and Emirati delegations at a dinner gathering for Sudan's visit to the UAE., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Royalty; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Presidents; Furnishings; Syria; Crowds; Gatherings; Airports; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Food; Flags; Clocks/Watches; Palm Trees; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Royalty; al-Assad, Hafez, 1930-2000; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top left clockwise: two views of performers in costumes performing a play, and a mosque with hills in the background., March to May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Mosques; Religious Sites; Mountains/Hills; Unknown Locations; Performing Arts; Costumes; Women; Group Portraits; Landscapes; Flags; Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Banners; Guns; Weapons; Arabic Writing; Officials; Audiences/Spectators; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils
  - From the top down: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with a representative of the Bahraini government arriving to Bahrain, with H.E. Sheikh Mubarak Bin Hamed and H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi behind them; H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with a representative of the Bahraini government; and a group of men including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) with H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem and members of the a delegation overseas., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Airports; Airplanes; Transportation; Officials; Presidents; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Telephones; Newspapers/Magazines; Arabic Writing; Bags/Purses; Women; Furnishings; Unknown Locations; Royalty; Bahrain; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top down: From the left: H.E. Sheikh Al Maktoum, Saif Ahmad Al Ghurair, H.E. Buti Bin Bishr, and an unidentified man; From the left: H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi, H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki, H.E. Sheikh Ahmad Al Hamed arriving at the airport in Syria; and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with Hafez Al-Assad at the Syrian reception of the Emirati Delegation., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Officials; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Drinks/Beverages; Airports; Flags; Gatherings; Crowds; Presidents; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Hats; Ceremonies; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Syria; Royalty; Bahrain; Political Leadership; al-Assad, Hafez, 1930-2000; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top left clockwise: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr with an unidentified man in a foreign country, a man performing for the UAE arrival to their country, and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan saluting in front of a Middle East Airlines airplane upon his arrival to an unknown country., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Officials; Men; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Presidents; Airplanes; Airports; Transportation; Ceremonies; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Performing Arts; Costumes; Unknown Locations; Royalty; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top down: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and the delegation of Abu Dhabi arriving in a country; Hafez Al-Assad awarding H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan a medal, with H.E. Saeed Al Darmaki in the middle; and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan standing with Jafaar Nimeiri., May 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Officials; Presidents; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Unknown Locations; Crowds; Gatherings; Ceremonies; Airports; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Facial Hair; Medals/Insignia; Clocks/Watches; Canes/Walking Sticks; Men; Royalty; Political Leadership; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009; al-Assad, Hafez, 1930-2000; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top left clockwise: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and Jafaar Nimeiri performing Al Ayala, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan having a private meeting with Hafez Al-Assad in Syria, a group of men including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in his office in Al Ain, and a group of men performing the Al Ayala dance., March to May 197222; AD_MC_093_ref4_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Guns; Weapons; Flags; Dancing; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Crowds; Gatherings; Restaurants/bars; Presidents; Officials; Paintings; Furnishings; Offices; Cigarettes; Smoking; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Syria; Al Ain, United Arab Emirates; Swords/Knives; Musical Instruments; Percussion Instruments; Flags; Royalty; Workers; Typewriters; Calendars; Telephones; Political Leadership; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009; al-Assad, Hafez, 1930-2000; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the top left clockwise: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with Emir Issa Bin Salman Al Khalifa of Bahrain, Jafaar Nimeiri with H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting the delegation of Syria during the UAE's arrival to the country, with Hafez Al-Assad to the left of Sheikh Zayed and H.E. Lieutenant General Khalfan Al Romaithi behind Sheikh Zayed., May to June 1972; AD_MC_093_ref4_000024_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Presidents; Government; Officials; Group Portraits; Paintings; Facial Hair; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Medals/Insignia; Ceremonies; Airplanes; Airports; Transportation; Crowds; Gatherings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Royalty; Bahrain; Political Leadership; Nimeiri, Jafaar, 1930-2009; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - The inside back cover of "Diplomatic and Political Engagements of the UAE 1972.", Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref4_000025_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Pakistan; Syria; United Arab Emirates; Unknown Locations
  - The back cover of "Diplomatic and Political Engagements of the UAE 1972.", Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref4_000026_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.5 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
- H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's Personal Trip to Murree, Pakistan 1970
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (middle) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) riding horses with a group of guards., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Murree, Pakistan; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Royalty; Presidents; Horses; Animals; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Forest/Woodlands; Men; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Officials; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan entering a car during his trip to Murree, Pakistan, with H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem (right of Zayed), Mohammed Bin Rawaya Al Khalili (behind Sheikh Zayed, left), H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim (behind Sulayem), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (on stairs on the right, wearing white) in the background., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Facial Hair; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Presidents; Royalty; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Buildings; Canes/Walking Sticks; Officials; Murree, Pakistan; Political Leadership
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) on a lawn., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Royalty; Presidents; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Forest/Woodlands; Murree, Pakistan; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) with a group of men., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Tea/Coffee; Furnishings; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Presidents; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Royalty; Carpets/Rugs; Drinks/Beverages; Murree, Pakistan; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - From the left: H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, Mohammed Bin Rawaya Al Khalili, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting under an umbrella with a platter of fruit., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Food; Umbrellas/Parasols; Forest/Woodlands; Facial Hair; Officials; Clocks/Watches; Murree, Pakistan; Arabic Writing; Mountains/Hills
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) riding horses with a group of guards., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Presidents; Officials; Streets/Roads; Electricity; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Horses; Animals; Forest/Woodlands; Murree, Pakistan; Royalty; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left, front) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right, front) sitting on a lawn with a group of guards., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Presidents; Officials; Royalty; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Forest/Woodlands; Murree, Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) playing carrom., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Royalty; Presidents; Officials; Card Games; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings; Murree, Pakistan; Carpets/Rugs; Political Leadership; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr with a telescope on a lawn next to Pakistani guards., 18 July 1970; AD_MC_093_ref5_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 12.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)